Guide to the Rand School of Social Science Records TAM.007
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VI: Publications, 1906-1955
  - Subseries VIF: Course Bulletins and Announcements, 1906-1955
    - Trade Union Training Courses: Spring Term, 1947 (Box 57, Folder 3)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:121
    - Bulletin: Fall Term, 1947 (Box 53, Folder 2)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:122
    - Trade Union Training Courses: Fall Term, 1947 (Box 53, Folder 2)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:123
    - Schedule of Courses, Rand school of Northern New Jersey: Fall Term, 1947 (Box 53, Folder 2)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:124
    - General Bulletin: Spring Term, 1948 (Box 53, Folder 2)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:125
    - Trade Union Training Courses: Spring Term, Jan 21, 1948 (Box 53, Folder 2)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:126
    - Schedule of Courses, Rand school of Northern New Jersey: Spring Term, Jan 20, 1948 (Box 53, Folder 2)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:127
    - Bulletin: Fall, 1948 (Box 53, Folder 2)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:128
    - Schedule of Courses: Fall, 1948 (Box 53, Folder 2)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:129
    - Schedule of Courses, Rand school of Northern New Jersey: Fall, 1948-1949 (Box 53, Folder 2)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:130
    - General Bulletin: Spring Term, 1949 (Box 53, Folder 2)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:131
    - Schedule of Courses, Rand school of Northern New Jersey: Spring Term, 1949 (Box 53, Folder 2)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:132
    - General Bulletin: Fall, 1949 (Box 53, Folder 2)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:133
    - Bulletin: Rand school of Northern New Jersey: Fall Term, Sep 22, 1949 (Box 53, Folder 2)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:134
    - General Bulletin: Spring, 1950 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:135
    - Bulletin: Spring Term, 1950 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:136
    - General Bulletin. Fall, 1950 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:137
    - General Bulletin. Spring, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:138
    - General Bulletin. Fall Term, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:139
    - General Bulletin. Spring, 1952 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:140
    - General Bulletin. Fall, 1952 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:141
    - Schedule of Courses. Labor-Management Relations and Trade Union Leadership Training Program, 1952 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:142
    - General Bulletin. Spring, 1953 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:143
    - Schedule of Courses. Labor-Management Relations and Trade Union Leadership Training Program: Spring, 1953 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:144
    - General Catalog: Fall Term, 1953 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:145
    - Catalog B: Labor-Management Relations and Trade Union Leadership Training Program: Fall, 1953 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:146
    - General Catalog: Spring Term, 1954 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:147
    - Catalog B: Labor-Management Relations and Trade Union Leadership Training Program: Spring, 1954 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:148
    - Spring Term Extension, 1954 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:149
    - General Catalog: Fall Term, 1954 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:150
    - Schedule of Courses. Labor-Management Relations and Trade Union Leadership Training Program: Fall, 1954 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:151
    - General Catalog: Spring, 1955 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:152
    - Catalog B: Spring, 1955 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:153
    - Schedule of Courses: Fall, 1955 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:154
    - Catalog B: Fall, 1955 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:155
  - Subseries VIG: Correspondence Course Lesson Books, 1913-1936, nd
    The seventh part of the publications series consists of 11 correspondence course lesson books. These lesson books, which contain individualized reading exercises and questions, relate to various courses in socialist history and thought, trade unionism, economics, and social history. Some of these books were written by such noted socialists as Scott Nearing, Algernon Lee, Anna A. Maley, Nathan Fine, and David P. Berenberg. The lesson books are arranged in alphabetical order according to the author's last name. A full bibliographical citation for each lesson book is located in the complete reel list for this collection.
    - Berenberg, David P. The Fundamentals of Socialism, 1919 (Box 53, Folder 4)
      Film R-7124, Reel 55
    - Fine, Nathan'. Trade Unionism in Theory and Practice, undated (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Henderson, Elinor. Introductory Studies of the Capitalist System. An outline Course for Socialist Groups, undated (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Kantorovitch, Haim. The Elements of Economics, undated (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Lee, Algernon. An Introduction to Scientific Socialism, undated (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Lee, Algernon. Social History and Economics, 1913, 1918 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Maley, Anna A. Elements of Socialism, 1914 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Nearing, Scott. The Human Element in Economics, 1919 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Ohsol, John G., et al. Social Problems and Socialist Policy, 1914 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Robinson, Jesse K. Civics Digest of Federal, State and City Governments, undated (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Shulman, Frederick. Basic Principles of Socialism in Outline Form with Suggested Readings, 1936 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Subseries VIH: Ephemera, 15 May 1911-3 February 1955, 1911-1955
    - Rand School Ephemera, 1911-1919 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Rand School Ephemera, 1920-1929 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Rand School Ephemera, 1930-1939 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Rand School Ephemera, 1940-1949 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Rand School Ephemera, 1950-1955 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Subseries VII: Press Releases, Sep 1926-Nov 1955, nd, 1926-1955
    The final two parts of the publications series contain ephemeral printed matter (XIII:F:8) and press releases (XIII:F:9). The ephemeral printed matter is arranged in chronological order and includes commemorative booklets, circular letters, programs, announcements, flyers, brochures, handbills, leaflets, and postcards. Some of the most interesting items in this part are the programs for the Rand School Ball of 1920, 1921, and 1922; ten leaflets relating to a series of political talks given by Scott Nearing before the Rand School's Current History class in 1924; a leaflet for Charles Beard's 1930-1931 symposium entitled, "American Civilization Today"; announcements for the Metropolitan opera and Broadway show benefits; and two booklets commemorating the 40th and 45th anniversaries of the Rand School. The press releases are also arranged in chronological order, with undated items placed at the end of the file. Most of the press releases contain general information about the Rand School as well as announcements of lectures and special events. There are also several speeches in this part which were given by Rand School faculty members and quest lecturers.
    - Press Releases, Sep 1926-Nov 1955 (Box 54, Folder 4)
- Series VII: Addendum, 1910-1955
  - Advertising: Correspondence and Documents, 1940s-1950s (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Advertising: Courses and Documents, 1932-1939, undated (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Advertisements, 1945-1955, undated (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - American Labor Party, Special Investigation Committee, 1938 (Box 55, Folder 4, Folder 1)
  - American Labor Yearbook, 1910s-1920s (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - American Labor Yearbook, 1920s (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - American Socialist Society (Including Minutes and Rand School Reports), 1910s-1940s (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - American Socialist Society, By Laws, undated (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Announcements (Press, Publications, Typescripts), 1919-1944, undated (Box 55, Folder 9, Folder 2)
  - Announcements (Press, Publications, Typescripts), 1944-1949 (Box 56, Folder 1, Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Announcements (Press, Publications, Typescripts), 1950-1955 (Box 56, Folder 2, Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Austria - Trade Unions, Socialist Party, undated (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Bibliographies, undated (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Board of Directors: Reports, Minutes, Correspondence, 1920s-1950s (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Bookstore, Library, 1940s-1950s, undated (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Brooklyn Forum, 1945. undated (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Cards, undated (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, 1930s-1940s (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Conferences, Symposiums, 1939, undated (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Contacts and Other Lists, undated (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Co-operative Educational Institute of Brownsville, 1923 (Box 57, Folder 5, Box 55, Disk 5)
  - Correspondence, 1923-1926 (Box 57, Folder 6, Box 55)
  - Correspondence, 1940s-1950s (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence Courses, 1930s (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, Afros, John, 1938-1939 (Box 57, Folder 9, Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Afros, John, 1940s (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, Mailly, Bertha H., 1917-1943 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, Publicity Related, 1940s-1950s (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Course Description, undated (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Course Feedback, undated (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Course Handouts, 1930s, undated (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Course Information - Afros [teacher], 1938-1939 (Box 55, Folder 8, Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Course Lists, 1920s-1940s (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Course Offerings, Bulletins, undated, 1910s (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Course Offerings, Bulletins, 1920s (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Course Offerings, Bulletins, 1931 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Course Offerings, Bulletins, 1932 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Course Offerings, Bulletins, 1933 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Course Offerings, Bulletins, 1934 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Course Offerings, Bulletins, 1935 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Course Offerings, Bulletins, 1936 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Course Offerings, Bulletins, 1937 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Course Offerings, Bulletins, 1938 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Course Offerings, Bulletins, 1939 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Course Offerings, Bulletins, 1940 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Course Offerings, Bulletins, 1941 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Course Offerings, Bulletins, 1942 (Box 58, Folder 42, Folder 17)
  - Course Offerings, Bulletins, 1943 (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - Course Offerings, Bulletins, 1944 (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - Course Offerings, Bulletins, 1945 (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - Course Offerings, Bulletins, 1946 (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - Course Offerings, Bulletins, 1947 (Box 58, Folder 22)
  - Course Offerings, Bulletins, 1948 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Course Offerings, Bulletins, 1949 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Course Offerings, Bulletins, 1950 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Course Offerings, Bulletins, 1951 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Course Offerings, Bulletins, 1952 (Box 58, Folder 5, Box 59)
  - Course Offerings, Bulletins, 1953 (Box 58, Folder 6, Box 59)
  - Course Offerings, Bulletins, 1954 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Course Offerings, Bulletins, 1955 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Course Outlines, 1930s-1940s (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Course: Points of Conflict in Modern Education, 1938-1939 (Box 55, Folder 11, Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Course Schedules, undated (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Course: Social Work, 1939 (Box 55, Folder 12, Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Curriculums, 1935 (Box 55, Folder 9, Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Curriculums for Future Classes, 1920s - 1930s (Box 59, Folder 14, Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Economics, undated, 1931 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Educational Council, undated, 1915-1920 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Event Announcements, 1940s (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Finances, 1929-1952 (Box 55, Folder 13, Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Finances, Invoices, 1930s-1940s (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - First Assistants' License Examinations - N.Y.C. High Schools, undated (Box 55, Folder 14, Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Handwritten Notes, undated (Box 55, Folder 15, Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Handwritten Notes and Messages (Rand School Administration), undated (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Handwritten Notes and Messages (Rand School Administration), undated, 1915-1950 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Index to Labor Articles, 1936-1950 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Index to Labor Articles, Subscriptions, undated, 1927-1939 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Index to Labor Articles, Subscriptions, undated, 1927-1939 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Index to Labor Articles, Subscriptions, undated, 1927-1939 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Index to Labor Articles, Subscriptions, 1940-1956 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Index to Labor Articles, Subscriptions, 1940-1956 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Index to Labor Periodicals, 1927 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Industrial Relations, Questionaires, undated, 1946 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Institution of Socialist Studies Bulletin, undated, 1951-1952 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Institution of Socialist Studies Bulletin, 1953-1955 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Intercollegiate Socialist Society, 1913, 1943, undated (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Job Opportunities, 1940, 1941 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Klein, Blossom - Personal Documents, 1949 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Labor History and Industrial Relations Typescripts, undated (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Labor Theater, undated (Box 61A, Folder 1)
  - Latin-American Affairs, May 1952-Oct 1955 (Box 61A, Folder 2)
  - Lecture Announcements, 1935-1944, undated (Box 61A, Folder 3)
  - Lecture Bureau, undated, 1938 (Box 61A, Folder 4)
  - Legal Documents (Agreements, Transcripts, Etc.), undated, 1919-1945 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Little Theater, undated (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Lusk Committee, 1919 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Mailing Lists, 1920s (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Mailing Lists, Etc., 1950s (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Manuscripts, undated (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Manuscripts: Labor and Socialist Topics, undated, 1919-1946 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Metropolitan Opera House Concert, 1932-1936 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Metropolitan Opera House Concert, 1949-1950 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Reports, Questionnaires, Notes, undated, 1930-1952 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Newark School of Social Sciences, undated, 1937-1947 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Other Organizations, undated, 1940-1946 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - People's House Bonds, 1927, 1928 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - People's House Cafeteria Records, undated, Apr 1918-Apr 1922 (Box 62A, Folder 1)
  - Press Releases, 1939-1947 (Box 62A, Folder 2)
  - Professors, Lecturers: Related Material, undated, 1932-1951 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Publicity, undated (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Publicity, 1922 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Publicity, Jul 1924-Nov 1924 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Publicity, Dec 1924-Apr 1925 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Publicity, undated, 1934-1936 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Publicity, 1931-1940 (Box 63, Folder 8, Folder 7)
  - Publicity, 1941-1955 (Box 63, Folder 9, Folder 8)
  - Rand School - Descriptions, 1919, undated (Box 63, Folder 10, Folder 9)
  - Rand School - Descriptions, undated, 1930-1939 (Box 63, Folder 11, Folder 10)
  - Rand School High School, 1935-1936, undated (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Rand School Relations with Labor Unions, undated, 1924-1948 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Research Department and Committee, undated (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Save the People's House, 1933 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Save the People's House - Socialist Party's Responses, undated, 1933 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Stag Dinners/Theatre Parties, 1933 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Steering Committee, 1946-1947 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Student Enrollment, 1933, undated (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Students Examination, undated (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Students Information, undated, 1938-1947 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Summer School, undated, 1932-1936 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Taft-Hartley Law, undated, 1947 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Tax Exemption, 1939-1954 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Tax Exemptions/IRS, 1947, 1950-1954 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Tchernavin, Tatiana Lecture: "Escape from the Soviets", 1934-1935 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Trade Union Institute, 1934-1947, undated (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Tuition Bills, 1954-1955 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - War Bond Rally, 1942 (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Women's Committee, 1930s (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Workmen's Circle, 1941-1942 (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - Youth Forum, 1946, undated (Box 64, Folder 18)
- Series VIII: Fragile Originals, undated
  - Rand School Photocopied Originals - Box 22 (Box 64A, Folder 1)
  - Rand School Photocopied Originals - Box 23 (Box 64A, Folder 2)
  - Rand School Photocopied Originals - Box 24 (Box 64A, Folder 3)
  - Rand School Photocopied Originals - Box 25 (Box 64A, Folder 4)
  - Rand School Photocopied Originals - Box 26 (Box 64A, Folder 5)
  - Rand School Photocopied Originals - Box 27 (Box 64A, Folder 6)
  - Rand School Photocopied Originals - Box 28 (Box 64A, Folder 7)
  - Rand School Photocopied Originals - Box 29 (Box 64A, Folder 8)
  - Rand School Photocopied Originals - Box 30 (Box 64A, Folder 9)
  - Rand School Photocopied Originals - Box 31 (Box 64A, Folder 10)
  - Rand School Photocopied Originals - Box 32 (Box 64A, Folder 11)
  - Rand School Photocopied Originals - Box 33 (Box 64A, Folder 12)
  - Rand School Photocopied Originals - Box 34 (Box 64A, Folder 13)
  - Rand School Photocopied Originals - Box 35 (Box 64A, Folder 14)
  - Rand School Photocopied Originals - Box 36 (Box 64A, Folder 15)
  - Rand School Photocopied Originals - Box 37 (Box 64A, Folder 16)
  - Rand School Photocopied Originals - Box 39 (Box 64A, Folder 17)
  - Rand School Photocopied Originals - Box 40 (Box 64A, Folder 18)
  - Rand School Photocopied Originals - Box 41 (Box 64A, Folder 19)
  - Rand School Photocopied Originals - Box 43 (Box 64A, Folder 20)
  - Rand School Photocopied Originals - Box 44 (Box 64A, Folder 21)
  - Rand School Photocopied Originals - Box 46 (Box 64A, Folder 22)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 1, Folder 1 through Box 1, Folder 3 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 1, Folder 5 through Box 1, Folder 6 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 1, Folder 7 through Box 1, Folder 8 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 1, Folder 9 through Box 1, Folder 15 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 2, Folder 2 through Box 2, Folder 11 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 2, Folder 17 through Box 2, Folder 27 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 3, Folder 1 through Box 3, Folder 8 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 3, Folder 9 through Box 3, Folder 14 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 4, Folder 1 through Box 4, Folder 34 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 5, Folder 5 through Box 5, Folder 15 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 6, Folder 1 through Box 6, Folder 20 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 7, Folder 7 through Box 7, Folder 26 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 8, Folder 1 through Box 8, Folder 10 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 9, Folder 1 through Box 9, Folder 12 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 10, Folder 1 through Box 10, Folder 13 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 11, Folder 1 through Box 11, Folder 10 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 12, Folder 1 through Box 12, Folder 15 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 13, Folder 1 through Box 13, Folder 21 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 14, Folder 1 through Box 15, Folder 20 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 16, Folder 1 through Box 16, Folder 20 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 17, Folder 5 through Box 19, Folder 15 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 20, Folder 2 through Box 20, Folder 16 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 21, Folder 1 through Box 23, Folder 12 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 24, Folder 2 through Box 25, Folder 13 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 26, Folder 1 through Box 26, Folder 14 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 27, Folder 2 through Box 27, Folder 16 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 28, Folder 2 through Box 28, Folder 16 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 29, Folder 1 through Box 29, Folder 13 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 59, Folders 2 through 9 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 59, Folder 10 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 59, Folder 10 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 59, Folder 10 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 59, Folder 11 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 59, Folders 12 through 15 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 59, Folder 16 and Box 60, Folder 1 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 60, Folders 1 and 2 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 60, Folder 2 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 60, Folder 3 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 60, Folder 3 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 60, Folder 3 (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 60, Folders 3 through 6 (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 60, Folder 6 (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 60, Folders 6 through 8 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 61, Folders 1 through 3 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 61, Folders 4 through 10 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 62, Folders 1 through 4 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 62, Folders 5 through 9 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 62, Folders 10 through 12 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 62, Folders 13 through 14 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 63, Folders 1 through 2 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 63, Folders 3 through 5 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Fragile Originals From Box 63, Folder 6 (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 63, Folders 7 through 8 (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 63, Folders 9 through 14 (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Oversize Photographs: portraits, group photos, dinner event photos, 1937-1942; undated (Box Shared Tamiment 006, Folder 9-10)
- Series IX: Embossing Stamp, undated; 2013.039
  - Rand School Embossing Stamp, unknown; 2013.039 (Box 70)